thelawofattraction.com 2015-06-11

# Privacy Policy

The Company of the Website respects and is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Data Protection Policy. We control this site from offices in the United Kingdom. All information gathered on this site is confidential. This website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. By becoming a member of the Inner Circle, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this policy. The following discloses our Data Protection Policy:

Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer’s “Internet Protocol” (IP) address. When a visitor requests a page on TheLawOfAttraction.com our web servers automatically recognise that visitor’s domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate use of the network, its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement activities and enquiries. We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. Our web servers do not automatically record email addresses of the visitors to our web sites.

We offer access to or may in the future offer access to some services that require registration. We may use your registration contact information to send notification to you of related products and services by email and/or postal mail. We will not share that information with any third party, save where we are required to do so by law or other applicable statute.

We may also request your email address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a survey or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to email newsletters, announcement lists or information about conferences and trade shows). Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. We maintain a strict policy on the protection of our data in accordance with the Data Protection Act, which means that we do not sell, rent, or otherwise give your email address to a third-party, without your consent or as permitted by this Data Protection Policy.

Disclosure of your information 

We will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the Site
  * Protect and defend the rights or property of the Site, or visitors to the Site
  * Identify persons who may be violating the law, our terms and conditions of use, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the Site or the computer equipment on which it is hosted (whether owned by the Site or a third party)
  * Fulfil a user’s order or request

Cookies and Tracking Information 

When you visit any of our websites (“Sites”), a cookie may be placed on your computer for a number of reasons, such as (a) to keep track of your shopping cart, (b) to recognise you when you return to our site, (c) to recognise whether a customer came to our site as a result of a promotion or advertisement with one of our partners sites or email campaign and (d) to track the sales made by customers referred to us from a 3rd party so that they can receive compensation under our affiliate program. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from The Company websites, you may not be able to view all the text on the screens, or to experience a personalised visit, or to subscribe to certain service and product offerings on our Sites.

We also collect anonymous visitor information about how you utilise our site, such as IP addresses, browser types (such as Chrome, Mozilla, Internet Explorer, Safari, etc.), referring pages and pages visited. We use this information (a) to perform anonymous statistical analysis of Web page traffic patterns, (b) to administer our Website and servers, and (c) to improve our services.

We may allow other companies, called third party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Site. These third party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Site. They automatically receive your IP Address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content. Further, these advertisers may also serve ads to you on other websites (including ads for our products and services) based on information collected from you while using the Site. For example, we may use Google’s “remarketing” service to target our ads to you based on your prior use of the Site when you visit on other sites in Google’s content network.

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such ad servers, ad networks, or their advertiser clients.

You should be aware that advertisers may target their ads to users based on certain user characteristics. If you respond to this type of targeted advertisement, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they were trying to reach.

You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting [Google’s Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Security and Data Retention 

We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.

You also have a right to be informed within a reasonably delay, on request, what information we hold about you, how we obtained it, and to whom we may pass it on. Such a request must be made in writing. The Company reserves the right as allowed under the act to levy a fee for this service.

We may from time to time send emails announcing new products and services. Except as stated above, the Company will not send you emails that you have not agreed to receive.

This privacy statement can change, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the privacy and security statement in effect at the time of collection. You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
